<resources>
    <string name="app_name" translatable="false">Mobile Check</string>

    <!-- URL TILES -->
    <string name="url_tiles" translatable="false">https://api.dev.netcheckapp.com/api/map?grid=%s&amp;pid=%d&amp;z=%d&amp;x=%1d&amp;y=%1d</string>

    <!-- Terms -->
    <string name="terms_header">Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="terms_body">
        I hereby agree that the NET CHECK GmbH, Ella-Barowsky-Straße 45-47, 10829 Berlin, the following
        data processed and transmitted for the purposes set out below.\n\n

        MOBILE CHECK includes a software extension (SDK) that collects technical data. For privacy
        MOBILE CHECK only collects the data in encrypted form and assigns it to a pseudonym.\n\n

        MOBILE CHECK collects the following data:\n\n

        Device information as MD5 hash:\n
        MAC Address, Android ID, Google Advertisement ID, Phone Number, IMSI\n\n

        Device Information:\n
        Program version and artificially generated device ID, device type and version\n\n

        Measuring Data:\n
        Time of use, position data of the device, mobile network data (access technology such as
        GSM, UMTS, LTE, etc.), CellId, LAC, MNC, MCC, available received signal strengths
        (RSSI, RSRP, CQI, ERFCN, etc.), device status (battery status, connection status),
        telephone status (rings, active call, waiting), WLAN information (connection status,
        theoretical speed, SSID, the first six digits of the BSSID), the first six digits of
        the IP address to identify the landline operator of the WLAN, length of a call and the
        volume of data consumed by the device\n\n

        To protect the privacy of the phone user, MOBILE CHECK does the following:\n
        A hash value (MD5) is formed from the MAC address (if applicable the Android ID or the
        Advertisement ID) of the mobile phone. This encryption is already done on the phone,
        so that the MAC address (or the Android ID or Advertisement ID) is not received.
        MOBILE CHECK only gets the hash value and uses it as a pseudonym to which all others
        collected data. The pseudonym is only used by MOBILE CHECK and its processor.
        It will not be disclosed to other third parties.\n\n

        MOBILE CHECK never collects data such as passwords, messages, emails nor access phonebook contacts or media content.\n\n

        MOBILE CHECK uses the data for purposes of analyzing mobile networks including issuing
        Optimization and expansion recommendations, market research and analysis of traffic flows including
        Catchment area, visitor frequency and location analyzes.\n
        Other recipients receive the data only in aggregated form, which does not make any conclusions about individual mobile phones
        or SIM cards. Data that can be assigned to specific mobile phones, in particular MAC addresses,
        IMSI and phone numbers (all hashed) will not be accessible to those recipients of the data.\n\n

        I can at any time under the settings of the app, the consent with the "On/Off switch" grant or revoke.
        With "on" I confirm the consent to the described transfer of data with the described methodology.
        I select "off" to not allow sharing. By revoking the consent becomes the legality
        the processing on the basis of the consent until the revocation is not affected.
    </string>

    <!-- About -->
    <string name="about_title">About / Imprint</string>
    <string name="about_body">
        MOBILE CHECK is an app to measure and rate the quality of communication networks.
        It is also possible to provide feedback on problems occur. By combining the active and comfort
        measurements in the background of many users in a community our maps and analysis are far
        ahead of time.\n\n

        Imprint\n\n

        Head Office\n
        NET CHECK GmbH, Ella-Barowsky-Straße 45-47, 10829 Berlin\n\n

        Contact\n\n

        Phone:+49 30 303080 600 Fax:+49 30 303080 668\n
        E-Mail: ncapp@netcheck.de\n\n

        Managing director\n
        Detlef Zernick\n\n

        Commercial information\n\n

        VAT number: DE201164592 Tax number:29/092/60238\n
        Tax office: Berlin für Körperschaften IVCommercial register number:Berlin HRB 73708 B\n\n

        Notice of liability\n
        Despite careful monitoring of its website, MOBILE CHECK cannot accept any responsibility for the
        content of external links. Such content is the sole responsibility of the respective website owner.
        No liability can be accepted for data protection violations or any other legal violations in
        connection with such links.\n\n

        Copyright\n
        All rights reserved. All texts, images, illustrations, documents and files are subject to
        copyright and to other laws for the protection of intellectual property. They may not be used
        for commercial purposes or duplicated or modified and reposted on other websites.
    </string>

    <!-- Legal Notes: -->
    <string name="legal_notes_disclaimer" translatable="false">The privacy specifications are provided in German language only!</string>
    <string name="legal_notes_body" translatable="false">
        \n\nPräambel\n\n

        1.	MOBILE CHECK ist eine Anwendung zur Erfassung anonymisierter Messgrößen zur Bestimmung der
        Qualität der Funknetzabdeckung und Performance von Datenverbindungen im Sinne von empfundener
        und technisch gemessener Qualität (QoS/QoE).\n
        2.	Die NET CHECK GmbH ist Betreiber von MOBILE CHECK.\n
        3.	Nutzer im Sinne dieser Vereinbarung ist eine natürliche oder juristische Person,
        welche die Smartphoneapplikation oder die NET CHECK Webseite benutzt.\n
        4.	Die Nutzungsvereinbarung kommt durch die Nutzung der Applikation oder der Webseite durch
        den Nutzer zustande. Die Annahme dieser Vereinbarung ist Voraussetzung für die Nutzung von MOBILE CHECK.\n
        5.	Der Betreiber behält sich ausdrücklich das Recht vor, natürlichen und juristischen Personen
        die Nutzung bzw. Registrierung sachgrundlos zu verweigern.

        \n\n§ 1 Geltungsbereich\n\n

        1.	Diese Nutzungsvereinbarung gilt für alle von MOBILE CHECK derzeit und künftig angebotenen
        Inhalte und Dienste. Sie betreffen das Nutzungsverhältnis zwischen dem Nutzer und dem Betreiber
        von MOBILE CHECK.
        2.	Nach Annahme der Nutzungsvereinbarung erhält der Nutzer von MOBILE CHECK die technische Möglichkeit,
        Testdaten aus dem Internet auf ein Endgerät zu übertragen (Download), Testdaten von einem Endgerät
        ins Internet zu senden (Upload) und die Laufzeit (Ping) von einem Endgerät zu einem Testserver
        zu ermitteln. Weiterhin kann die Performance für Webseiten (Browsing) und Youtube überprüft werden.
        3.	Der Betreiber kann die vorliegende Nutzungsvereinbarung jederzeit aktualisieren oder ändern.
        Sollte der Nutzer der aktualisierten Nutzungsvereinbarung widersprechen oder die Annahme dieser
        unterlassen, endet das Nutzungsrecht unmittelbar.
        4.	Allgemeine Geschäftsbedingungen des Nutzers sowie Abänderungen dieser Nutzungsvereinbarung
        finden keine Anwendung.

        \n\n§ 2 Nutzungsverhältnis\n\n

        1.	Das Nutzungsverhältnis beginnt mit der Annahme dieser Vereinbarung durch den Nutzer.\n
        2.	Das Nutzungsverhältnis kann jederzeit durch den Nutzer beendet werden. Hierzu ist die
        Applikation zu löschen. Mit der Registrierung als Nutzer erhält dieser vom Betreiber ein individuelles
        Zugangsrecht für die erweiterten Dienste bei MOBILE CHECK. Das Zugangsrecht gilt nur für den Nutzer
        und ist nicht übertragbar.\n
        3.	Das Recht des Betreibers und des Nutzers zur fristlosen Kündigung aus wichtigem Grunde
        bleibt unberührt.

        \n\n§ 3 Rechte und Pflichten des Nutzers\n\n

        1.	Der Nutzer erhält mit Beginn des Nutzungsverhältnisses das Recht, MOBILE CHECK und die freigegeben
        Funktionalitäten gemäß dieser Nutzungsvereinbarung zu verwenden.\n
        2.	Der Nutzer erklärt sich einverstanden, dass die von ihm zur Verfügung gestellten Daten
        anonymisiert für andere Nutzer oder weitere Dritte sichtbar sein können.\n
        3.	Der Nutzer erwirbt außerhalb der bestimmungsgemäßen Nutzung von MOBILE CHECK keinerlei Rechte.\n
        4.	Der Nutzer ist verpflichtet, die rechtlichen Vorschriften einzuhalten und Angebote und
        Dienste von MOBILE CHECK nicht zu rechtswidrigen Zwecken zu gebrauchen.\n
        5.	Die Angebote und Dienste von MOBILE CHECK dürfen nur zu den in Absatz 1 der Präambel genannten
        Zwecken gebraucht werden.\n
        6.	Verboten sind Handlungen des Nutzers, die geeignet sind, die Angebote und Dienste von
        MOBILE CHECK zu beeinträchtigen oder funktionsuntauglich zu machen. Der Nutzer ist verpflichtet,
        dem Betreiber alle Schäden zu ersetzen, welche aus einem Verstoß gegen die genannten Pflichten
        oder Rechte Dritter resultieren. Hierzu gehören auch mittelbare Schäden und Vermögensschäden.
        Der Nutzer stellt den Betreiber von sämtlichen Ansprüchen Dritter frei, welche aus diesem Verstoß
        resultieren, außer er hat diesen Verstoß nicht zu vertreten.

        \n\n§ 4 Verantwortlichkeit für Inhalte, Verweise und Links\n\n

        1.	Falls der Nutzer über Links bei MOBILE CHECK auf fremde Internetseiten gelangt, liegt die
        Verantwortlichkeit ausschließlich bei den Anbietern dieser Seiten. Der Betreiber macht sich
        die Inhalte dieser Seiten nicht zu eigen. Jegliche Haftung oder Gewährleistung des Betreibers
        für die Inhalte der verlinkten Seiten ist ausgeschlossen. Eine automatische kurzzeitige
        Zwischenspeicherung fremder Informationen ist aufgrund der gewählten Aufruf- und Verlinkungsmethodik
        ausgeschlossen, so dass sich auch insoweit keine Verantwortlichkeit des Betreibers hierfür ergibt.\n
        2.	Zum Zeitpunkt der Verlinkung waren für den Betreiber keine rechtswidrigen Inhalte auf den
        verlinkten Seiten erkennbar. Auf aktuelle und künftige Änderungen der verlinkten Seiten hat der
        Betreiber keinen Einfluss.\n

        \n\n§ 5 Zugriff und Verfügbarkeit von MOBILE CHECK\n\n

        1.	Der Internetzugang und das Kommunikationsequipment sind nicht Bestandteile dieser Vereinbarung.\n
        2.	Der Betreiber ist berechtigt, MOBILE CHECK jederzeit dem jeweiligen Stand der Technik und den rechtlichen Erfordernissen anzupassen.

        \n\n§ 6 Leistungsstörungen\n\n
        1.	Aufgrund der Struktur des Internets hat der Betreiber keinen Einfluss auf die Datenübertragung
        im Internet und übernimmt keine Verantwortung für die Verfügbarkeit, Zuverlässigkeit und Qualität
        von Telekommunikationsnetzen, Datennetzen und technischen Einrichtungen Dritter. Störungen aufgrund
        höherer Gewalt hat der Betreiber nicht zu vertreten.\n
        2.	Der Betreiber kann die Nutzung von MOBILE CHECK ganz oder teilweise sperren oder den Zugang zu
        MOBILE CHECK ganz oder teilweise beschränken, wenn NET CHECK technisch überlastet oder gestört ist bzw.
        eine solche Überlastung oder Störung einzutreten droht. In diesen Fällen ist der Betreiber bemüht,
        die vollständige Funktionsfähigkeit umgehend wiederherzustellen.\n
        3.	Aufgrund von Wartungsarbeiten am System kann die Funktionsfähigkeit von MOBILE CHECK kurzzeitig
        eingeschränkt sein oder nicht zur Verfügung stehen.

        \n\n§ 7 Datenschutz und Datensicherheit\n\n

        1.	Die für die Durchführung und Abwicklung der bei MOBILE CHECK angebotenen erweiterten Dienste
        erforderlichen personenbezogenen Daten des Nutzers werden nach Maßgabe der gesetzlichen
        Bestimmungen des Datenschutzgesetzes der Bundesrepublik Deutschland und des Landes Berlin
        erhoben, gespeichert und verarbeitet.\n
        2.	Bei der Nutzung der Smartphoneapplikation werden, außer den freiwilligen Angaben, keine
        personenbezogenen Daten erfasst und gespeichert. Folgende technische Daten werden zum Betreiber
        übertragen und gespeichert:\n
        a. Zeitpunkt\n
        b. Positionsdaten\n
        c. Messergebnisse\n
        d. Programmversion und ID\n
        e. Gerätetyp und Version\n
        f. Mobilfunknetzdaten:\n
        Zugangstechnologie (GSM, UMTS, LTE usw.), CellId, LAC, MNC, MCC, Pegel)\n
        3.	Bei der Nutzung der Komfortmessung werden zusätzlich folgende Daten anonymisiert, übertragen
        und gespeichert:\n
        a. Gerätezustand: Batteriestatus, Verbindungsstatus, Telefonzustand (klingelt, aktives Telefonat,
        wartend)\n
        b. Mobilfunknetzdaten: verfügbare Pegelwerte\n
        c. WLAN: Verbindungsstatus, Betreiber, theoretische Geschwindigkeit, ID\n
        d. Nutzungsdaten: Datenverbrauch pro App insgesamt sowie im Mobilnetz, Nutzerkonten ID als HASH-Wert\n
        4.	Die in Absatz 1 angegebenen Daten werden ausschließlich zu technischen oder statistischen
        Zwecken benötigt; ein Abgleich mit anderen Datenbeständen oder eine nicht anonymisierte Weitergabe
        an Dritte, auch in Auszügen, findet nicht statt.\n
        5.	Die Nutzung der angebotenen Serviceleistungen und Dienste (Bestellung von Informationsmaterial
        und Newslettern sowie Datenbankselbsteinträge usw.) seitens des Nutzers erfolgt ausdrücklich und
        auf freiwilliger Basis. Personenbezogene Daten, die zur Zweckerfüllung notwendigerweise zu
        speichern sind, werden unmittelbar nach dieser durch den Betreiber gelöscht.\n
        6.	In jedem Fall werden die angegebenen persönlichen Daten ausschließlich für die Übersendung
        der gewünschten Informationen bzw. für die bei dem einzelnen Formular ggf. explizit genannten
        anderen Zwecke verarbeitet. Sofern es zur Beantwortung der Anfrage erforderlich ist, werden
        die eingetragenen Daten an die fachlich zuständige Stelle weitergeleitet. Darüber hinaus werden
        diese Daten nicht an Dritte weitergegeben.\n
        7.	Der Nutzer gestattet dem Betreiber, Auskunft über die verarbeiteten und gespeicherten Daten
        des Betroffenen nach Maßgabe des Bundes und Berliner Datenschutzgesetzes zu geben.\n
        8.	Der Nutzer stimmt der Verarbeitung seiner personenbezogenen Daten nach Maßgabe dieser
        Vereinbarung ausdrücklich zu.\

        \n\n§ 8 Urheberrechtsschutz und Bildnachweis\n\n

        1.	Die Inhalte dürfen nicht verändert und ohne schriftliche Genehmigung der jeweiligen Rechtsinhaber
        in anderen elektronischen oder gedruckten Publikationen genutzt werden. Dieses gilt auch für die
        Reproduktion, dauerhafte Speicherung oder das Versenden von Inhalten, die auf diesen Webseiten
        eingestellt sind.\n
        2.	Falls nicht anders angegeben, unterliegen alle Seiten von MOBILE CHECK dem
        Urheberrecht (Copyright). Dies gilt insbesondere für Texte, Bilder, Logos, Grafiken, Ton- und
        Videodateien einschließlich deren Anordnung auf den Webseiten.\n
        3.	Alle innerhalb des Internetangebotes genannten und ggf. durch Dritte geschützten Marken- und
        Warenzeichen unterliegen uneingeschränkt den Bestimmungen des jeweils gültigen Kennzeichenrechts
        und den Eigentums- bzw. Besitzrechten der jeweiligen eingetragenen Eigentümer. Durch die bloße
        Nennung bei MOBILE CHECK ist nicht der Schluss zu ziehen, dass Markenzeichen nicht durch Rechte
        Dritter geschützt sind.\n
        4.	Ein Verstoß gegen diese Bestimmungen verpflichtet zur sofortigen Vernichtung aller
        ausgedruckten oder heruntergeladenen Inhalte. Die Geltendmachung von Schadensersatzansprüchen bleibt
        vorbehalten.\n
        5.	In den vorliegenden Inhalten werden Marken und geschäftliche Bezeichnungen verwendet; auch
        wenn diese nicht als solche gekennzeichnet sind, gelten die entsprechenden gesetzlichen Bestimmungen.

        \n\n§ 9 Ausschluss von Gewährleistung und Haftung\n\n

        1.	Die Inhalte von MOBILE CHECK werden unter Ausschluss jeglicher Gewährleistung zur Verfügung gestellt,
        insbesondere wird nicht für deren Richtigkeit, Vollständigkeit oder deren Eignung für bestimmte
        Verwendungszwecke sowie im Hinblick auf die Inhalte für deren Freiheit von Rechten Dritter und
        die Nichtverletzung geistigen Eigentums gehaftet.\n
        2.	Der Betreiber kann jederzeit ohne vorherige Ankündigung Änderungen am Inhalt dieser Webseite
        vornehmen. Der Betreiber ist um ständige Aktualität bemüht, ist jedoch nicht zur Aktualisierung
        des Inhalts dieser Webseite verpflichtet.\n
        3.	Der Betreiber übernimmt keine Gewähr für die Erreichbarkeit und technische Verwertbarkeit der
        Internetseiten oder übermittelter Dateien Dritter.\n
        4.	Die Nutzung der bei MOBILE CHECK zur Verfügung gestellten Inhalte erfolgt auf alleinige Gefahr
        des Nutzers. Für mögliche Schäden jedweder Art übernehmen der Betreiber bzw. bei MOBILE CHECK registrierte
        oder bei MOBILE CHECK erwähnte Dritte keinerlei Haftung.\n
        5.	Absatz 4 gilt nicht, sofern Schäden vorsätzlich entstanden sind oder gesetzliche Regelungen zur
        Haftung zwingend vorgeschriebenen sind.

        \n\n§ 10 Entgelte\n\n

        1.	Die Registrierung bei MOBILE CHECK sowie die Nutzung der angebotenen Dienste und Services sind,
        soweit der Betreiber Entgelte oder Kosten nicht ausdrücklich benennt, kostenfrei.

        \n\n§ 11 Gerichtsstand und anwendbares Recht\n\n

        1.	Gerichtsstand für etwaige Streitigkeiten im Zusammenhang mit dieser Vereinbarung ist Berlin.
        Gesetzlich zwingende Gerichtsstände bleiben unberührt.
        2.	Es gilt das Recht der Bundesrepublik Deutschland mit Ausnahme seiner kollisionsrechtlichen
        Bestimmungen.
    </string>

    <string name="privacy_policy">Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="sdk" translatable="false">MQ Library</string>

    <string name="about_phone_num">+49 30 303080 600</string>
    <string name="about_email" translatable="false">ncapp@netcheck.de</string>

    <string name="agree">I agree</string>
    <string name="disagree">I disagree</string>

    <string name="enable">Enable</string>
    <string name="disable">Disable</string>

    <!-- Menu -->
    <string name="history">History</string>
    <string name="results">Test Results</string>
    <string name="network_status">Network Status</string>
    <string name="ping">Ping</string>
    <string name="download">Download</string>
    <string name="upload">Upload</string>
    <string name="browsing">Browsing</string>
    <string name="youtube">YouTube</string>
    <string name="performance">Performance</string>

    <!-- Drawer menu -->
    <string name="about">About</string>
    <string name="maps">Maps</string>
    <string name="legal_notes">Legal Notes</string>
    <string name="settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="tile_map">Tile Map</string>
    <string name="heat_map">Heat Map</string>
    <string name="tool_map">Tool Map</string>

    <!-- Permissions -->
    <string name="permission_explanation">This app collects location data to enable the monitoring of network parameter for coverage evaluation even when the app is closed or not in use. </string>

    <!-- Settings -->
    <string name="sdk_show_title">MQ2 Dialog</string>
    <string name="sdk_show_body">show the dialog tu use the MQ-Lib</string>
    <string name="sdk_agree_title">Enable MQ2</string>
    <string name="sdk_agree_body">agree/disagree usage of MQ-Lib</string>
    <string name="tool_abort_title">Stop Tool</string>
    <string name="tool_abort_body">Do you want to stop the tool?</string>
    <string name="tutorial_agree_title">Enable Tutorial</string>
    <string name="tutorial_agree_body_map">show tutorial on tile map page</string>
    <string name="tutorial_agree_body_main">show tutorial on main page</string>
    <string name="tutorial_agree_body_tool">show tutorial on tool page</string>

    <!-- Network Status -->
    <string name="cellular_information">Cellular Information</string>
    <string name="attached">Attached</string>
    <string name="sim_not_found">Sim card not found</string>
    <string name="yes">Yes</string>
    <string name="no">No</string>
    <string name="provider">Provider</string>
    <string name="technology">Technology</string>
    <string name="tel_number">Telephone number</string>
    <string name="level">Level</string>
    <string name="mcc_mnc">MCC-MNC</string>
    <string name="mcc" translatable="false">MCC</string>
    <string name="mnc" translatable="false">MNC</string>
    <string name="lac">LAC</string>
    <string name="tac" translatable="false">TAC</string>
    <string name="cell_id">Cell ID</string>
    <string name="sim_operator">SIM operator</string>
    <string name="sim_number">SIM number</string>
    <string name="sim_country">SIM country</string>

    <string name="wifi_info">Wi-Fi Information</string>
    <string name="connected">Connected</string>
    <string name="wifi_not_connected">Wi-Fi not detected</string>
    <string name="ssid">SSID</string>
    <string name="bssid">BSSID</string>
    <string name="mac">MAC</string>
    <string name="ip_address">IP Address</string>
    <string name="link_speed">Link speed</string>
    <string name="capabilities">Capabilities</string>
    <string name="frequency">Frequency</string>
    <string name="ip_config">IP Configuration</string>

    <string name="device_info">Device information</string>
    <string name="manufacturer">Manufacturer</string>
    <string name="model">Model</string>
    <string name="sim_status">SIM status</string>
    <string name="battery_status">Battery status</string>

    <string name="refresh">Refresh</string>
    <string name="missing_permission">Missing permission</string>
    <string name="location_not_found">Location not found</string>
    <string name="location_disabled">Location disabled</string>
    <string name="location_enable">Enable location to continue.</string>
    <string name="location_permission_disabled">Location permission disabled!</string>

    <string name="attached_body">Indicates if you are attached to a cellular network.</string>
    <string name="cell_id_body">A Cell ID (Cell identification) identifies uniquely the cell in which your device is logged in.</string>
    <string name="sim_country_body">The country of your domestic network.</string>
    <string name="lac_body">The Location Area Code (LAC) refers to the current location area of a mobile phone within a mobile network.  </string>
    <string name="level_body">The level indicates you how good is your reception signal.\ndBm is an electrical power unit
                                   (in dB) referenced to 1 milliwatt (mW). Typical range is between -49 dBm und -115 dBm.</string>
    <string name="mcc_mnc_body">The abbreviation MCC stands for Mobile Country Code. Together with the Mobile Network Code (MNC),
                                it is used to identify each mobile network.  </string>
    <string name="sim_operator_body">The domestic network of your SIM card, if the notification is activated by your provider.</string>
    <string name="tel_number_body">The phone number saved on your device. Your device might not display the new phone number
                                     immediately after changing the SIM card.\n\nPLEASE NOTE: We don\'t register this number! It is only shown here.</string>
    <string name="provider_body">The provider of your mobile network.</string>
    <string name="technology_body">This field indicates which mobile broadcast standard is being used at the moment
                                   (GSM, GPRS, EDGE, UMTS, HSDPA, HSDPA+ LTE, LTE Advanced).</string>
    <string name="ip_address_body">Each device within a network has an IP address (IP = Internet Protocol). It is used for the identification
                                   and addressing of a device. Thus, it is ensured that the data stream arrives at the correct device.</string>
    <string name="serial_num_body">Every SIM card has a serial number (ICCID).\n\nPLEASE NOTE: We don´t register this number!
                                   It will only appear here.</string>
    <string name="bssid_body">The BSSID is the MAC address of your router or access point.</string>
    <string name="capabilities_body">Indicates the security standards for wireless network access supported by your device.</string>
    <string name="frequency_body">Informs about the channel frequency of your wireless connection.</string>
    <string name="mac_body">Your MAC address. This address is assigned uniquely to each suitable network device. It is also
                            known as Ethernet ID, Airport ID, Wi-Fi address or physical address.</string>
    <string name="link_speed_body">(also known as data rate). The link speed specifies how much data can theoretically be
                                   transmitted within a time unit over a transmission channel. </string>
    <string name="ssid_body">SSID is the acronym for Service Set Identifier. The SSID is the name of your Wi-Fi network. </string>
    <string name="connected_body">Indicates if you are connected to a wireless network.</string>
    <string name="sim_status_body">The SIM status reports whether there are problems with the SIM card.
        \n\nReady:\nno problems\n\nPIN/PUK required:\nPIN or PUK code must be entered to unlock the SIM card
        \n\nABSENT:\nSIM card not inserted</string>
    <string name="sim_number_body">Every SIM card has a serial number (ICCID).
        \n\nPLEASE NOTE: We don´t register this number! It will only appear here.</string>
    <string name="ip_config_body">IP address and information about your network are displayed here.</string>

    <!-- Selection -->
    <string name="ok">OK</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="proceed">Proceed</string>

    <!-- Sim card status -->
    <string name="absent">ABSENT</string>
    <string name="ready">READY</string>
    <string name="not_ready">NOT READY</string>
    <string name="error">ERROR</string>
    <string name="restricted">RESTRICTED</string>
    <string name="locked">LOCKED</string>
    <string name="disabled">DISABLED</string>
    <string name="pin_required">PIN REQUIRED</string>
    <string name="puk_required">PUK REQUIRED</string>
    <string name="unknown">UNKNOWN</string>

    <!-- Filters -->
    <string name="test">Test</string>
    <string name="reset">Reset</string>
    <string name="problems">Show problems</string>
    <string name="best">Best</string>
    <string name="average">Average</string>
    <string name="avg">Avg</string>

    <string name="place_select">Place: %s</string>
    <string name="test_select">Test: %s</string>
    <string name="signal_level">Signal level</string>

    <!-- Map -->
    <string name="date_technology">Date &amp; Technology</string>
    <string name="date_time">Date &amp; Time</string>
    <string name="date">Date</string>
    <string name="place">Place</string>
    <string name="test_results">Net Test Results</string>
    <string name="zoom_warning">Zoom in to see the tiles!</string>
    <string name="select_marker_warning">Select marker to show results</string>
    <string name="select_tile_warning">Click on a tile to show results</string>

    <string name="my_test">My Tests</string>
    <string name="connection">Connection</string>

    <!-- Place dialog -->
    <string name="place_title">Where are you…</string>
    <string name="bus_streetcar">Bus</string>
    <string name="car_vehicle">Car </string>
    <string name="other">Other</string>
    <string name="outdoors">Outdoors</string>
    <string name="train">Train</string>
    <string name="indoors">Indoors</string>

    <!-- Dialogs -->
    <string name="data_usage_title">Notice</string>
    <string name="data_usage_body">The net test can result in increased data usage.
      Depending on your contract, additional costs may be incurred.</string>
    <string name="test_active_title">Another Test Active</string>
    <string name="test_active_body">You cannot run two tests at the time.</string>
    <string name="test_cancel_title">Stop test</string>
    <string name="test_cancel_message">Stop the current test?</string>
    <string name="test_delete_title">Delete test</string>
    <string name="test_delete_message">Do you really want to delete this test?</string>
    <string name="data_roaming_title">Enable Mobile Data</string>
    <string name="data_roaming_message">This test requires user to disable wifi and use mobile data.</string>

    <!-- Permission explanation -->
    <string name="type">Type</string>
    <string name="strength">Strength</string>
    <string name="permission_explain_title">Permissions Required</string>
    <string name="permission_explain_location">We require the location permission to receive your position during the tests.</string>
    <string name="permission_explain_phone">Please enable the call permission to register call drops. There is no personal information like phone number shared. </string>
    <string name="permission_explain_background">This app collects location data to enable the monitoring
        of network parameter for coverage evaluation even when the app is closed or not in use. For full support of this feature the background location permission is required. </string>
    <string name="permission_explain_sdk"> We will show you now an opt-in dialog explaining the features and methods we are using to collect network parameter. </string>

    <!-- Intent -->
    <string name="send_email">Send Email: </string>
    <string name="tel">Tel: </string>
    <string name="file_removal_error">Error while deleting the file</string>
    <string name="save_file_error">Error while saving file to storage</string>

    <!-- Browsing KPI -->
    <string name="latency">Latency</string>
    <string name="load_time">Load time</string>
    <string name="load_ratio" translatable="false">Ratio</string>

    <!-- YouTube KPI -->
    <string name="freeze">Freeze</string>
    <string name="video_quality">Video quality</string>

    <!-- States -->
    <string name="unreachable">Unreachable</string>
    <string name="canceled">Canceled</string>

    <string name="good">Good</string>
    <string name="bad">Bad</string>
    <string name="poor">Poor</string>

    <string name="loading">Loading</string>
    <string name="started">Started</string>
    <string name="testing">Testing</string>

    <string name="wifi" translatable="false">Wi-Fi</string>
    <string name="mobile" translatable="false">Mobile</string>
    <string name="disconnected">Disconnected</string>
    <string name="failed">Failed</string>
    <string name="none">None</string>

    <string name="site_not_reachable">Site not reachable</string>
    <string name="connection_not_available">Connection not available</string>
    <string name="wait_for_test">Test not finished!</string>

    <string name="tool" translatable="false">Tool</string>
    <string name="ping_rtt" translatable="false">Ping RTT</string>
    <string name="operator">Operator</string>
    <string name="plmn" translatable="false">PLMN</string>
    <string name="psc_uarf" translatable="false">PSC/UARF</string>
    <string name="cid" translatable="false">CID</string>
    <string name="plmn_lac" translatable="false">PLMN/LAC</string>
    <string name="dbm" translatable="false">dbm</string>
    <string name="network_type" translatable="false">Network type</string>
    <string name="additional_type" translatable="false">Additional type</string>
    <string name="sim_slot" translatable="false">Sim slot</string>
    <string name="signal_quality" translatable="false">Signal quality</string>
    <string name="arfcn" translatable="false">arfcn</string>
    <string name="gsmber" translatable="false">gsmber</string>
    <string name="wcdmapsc" translatable="false">wcdmapsc</string>
    <string name="ltepci" translatable="false">ltepci</string>
    <string name="rssnr" translatable="false">rssnr</string>
    <string name="cqi" translatable="false">cqi</string>
    <string name="lteta" translatable="false">lteta</string>
    <string name="ltebw" translatable="false">ltebw</string>
    <string name="nrsinr" translatable="false">nrsinr</string>
    <string name="nrssrsrq" translatable="false">nrssrsrq</string>
    <string name="nrssrsrp" translatable="false">nrssrsrp</string>
    <string name="bandwidths" translatable="false">Bandwidths</string>
    <string name="traffic_info" translatable="false">Traffic Info</string>
    <string name="bytes_tx" translatable="false">Bytes Tx</string>
    <string name="bytes_rx" translatable="false">Bytes Rx</string>
    <string name="battery_info" translatable="false">Battery Info</string>
    <string name="health" translatable="false">Health</string>
    <string name="sensor_info" translatable="false">Sensor info</string>
    <string name="light" translatable="false">Light</string>
    <string name="magnet_x" translatable="false">Magnet X</string>
    <string name="magnet_y" translatable="false">Magnet Y</string>
    <string name="magnet_z" translatable="false">Magnet Z</string>
    <string name="proximity" translatable="false">Proximity</string>
    <string name="pressure" translatable="false">Pressure</string>
    <string name="humidity" translatable="false">Humidity</string>
    <string name="data_state">Data State</string>
    <string name="data_activity" translatable="false">Data Activity</string>
    <string name="ipv4_address" translatable="false">IPv4 Address</string>
    <string name="ipv6_address" translatable="false">IPv6 Address</string>
    <string name="call_state">Call State</string>
    <string name="nw_capacity_dl">NW Capacity DL</string>
    <string name="nw_capacity_ul">NW Capacity UL</string>
    <string name="mobile_kbps_dl" translatable="false">Mobile Kbps DL</string>
    <string name="mobile_kbps_ul" translatable="false">Mobile Kbps UL</string>
    <string name="total_kbps_dl">Total Kbps DL</string>
    <string name="total_kbps_ul">Total Kbps UL</string>
    <string name="s_state" translatable="false">s_state</string>
    <string name="rssi" translatable="false">RSSI</string>
    <string name="longitude" translatable="false">Longitude</string>
    <string name="latitude" translatable="false">Latitude</string>
    <string name="altitude" translatable="false">Altitude</string>
    <string name="speed">Speed</string>
    <string name="g" translatable="false">G</string>
    <string name="pci_psc_bsic" translatable="false">PCI/PSC/BSIC</string>
    <string name="e_u_arfcn" translatable="false">(E/U)ARFCN</string>
    <string name="reg" translatable="false">REG</string>
    <string name="tac_lac" translatable="false">TAC/LAC</string>
    <string name="rsrp_rscp_rxlev" translatable="false">RSRP/RSCP/RxLev</string>
    <string name="rsrq" translatable="false">RSRQ</string>
    <string name="ta" translatable="false">TA</string>
    <string name="mobile_network">Mobile Network</string>
    <string name="data">Data</string>
    <string name="cell_info">Cell Info</string>
    <string name="signal_power">Signal Power</string>
    <string name="ping_unit" translatable="false">ms</string>
    <string name="empty" translatable="false"> </string>

    <!-- Tutorial -->
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="done">Done</string>

    <string name="toggle_personal_results">Enable personal results created once you finished testing.</string>
    <string name="select_filter_results">Use filters to view results of others presented as tiles on the map.</string>
    <string name="select_tile_results">Select tile to learn about providers and connection in given area.</string>
    <string name="select_marker_results">Select marker to learn about connection in given area based on your test.</string>
    <string name="view_connection_level">Blue stands for good, red stands for bad connection.</string>
    <string name="select_map_controls">Map controls.</string>
    <string name="toggle_clustering">Toggle clustering.</string>

    <string name="select_test_type">Choose between performance, youtube or browsing test type.</string>
    <string name="select_user_results">View past test results.</string>
    <string name="select_status_page">View network status information.</string>
    <string name="select_test_place">Select place where test is taken.</string>
    <string name="present_conn_type">View connection type and availability.</string>

    <string name="present_graph_type">Graphs presenting signal status and ping values.</string>
    <string name="toggle_follow_driver">Toggle driver following on the map.</string>
    <string name="toggle_tool">Toggle tool.</string>
    <string name="clear_map">Clear map.</string>
    <string name="view_map_settings">View map settings.</string>
    <string name="view_signal_level">Green stands for good, orange stands for bad signal.</string>
    <string name="view_device_status">View status of connection, sensors, traffic and battery.</string>

    <string name="traffic_kbits" translatable="false">kbit/s</string>
    <string name="traffic_mbits" translatable="false">mbit/s</string>
    <string name="ping_ms" translatable="false">ms</string>
    <string name="ping_s" translatable="false">s</string>
    <string name="minimum_test_selection_warning">Minimum test selection is one!</string>
    <string name="warning_select_place">You must select place to continue!</string>
    <string name="map_line_thickness">Map\nthickness</string>
    <string name="signal_line_thickness">Signal\nthickness</string>
    <string name="close">Close</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="report_center">Report Center</string>

</resources>